<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/reuters/world" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[Reuters.com is your online source for the latest world news stories and current events, ensuring our readers up to date with any breaking news developments - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><image/><url> https://www.reuters.com/pf/resources/images/reuters/logo-vertical-default-512x512.png?d=116</url><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/<lastbuilddate> 2023 年 12 月 19 日星期二 02:24:26 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Blinken, in call with Saudi counterpart, condemns Houthis for Red Sea attacks]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken held a call with Saudi Arabian Foreign Minister Prince Faisal bin Farhan on Monday in which he condemned attacks by Yemen's Houthi movement on commercial vessels in international waters in the Red Sea, the State Department said on Monday.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 01:31:10 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 5L42QJZRKBJTJK2WM4RWUZFZEU</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/blinken-call-with-saudi-counterpart-condemns-houthis-red-sea-attacks-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Kanishka Singh, Costas Pitas]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Taiwan reports another suspected Chinese weather balloon crossing Taiwan Strait]]></title><description><![CDATA[A suspected Chinese weather balloon flew across the sensitive Taiwan Strait on Monday but stayed well north of Taiwan, the island's defence ministry said on Tuesday, the third time this month Taipei has reported them nearby.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 01:30:02 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> SUGQ532YDZJGLFHHHUT55YKHJA</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/taiwan-reports-another-suspected-chinese-weather-balloon-crossing-taiwan-strait-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tokyo prosecutors search offices of key ruling party faction]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tokyo prosecutors on Tuesday searched the headquarters of a powerful political faction within the ruling Liberal Democratic Party (LDP), public broadcaster NHK reported, in connection with the biggest fundraising scandal to engulf the party in decades.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 01:15:26 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> U5DWJGIUBZKZ3KMAM44R3CALM4</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/tokyo-prosecutors-raid-offices-ruling-ldp-factions-over-funds-scandal-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Raided Gaza hospital not functioning, patients evacuated- WHO]]></title><description><![CDATA[A north Gaza hospital that Israeli troops raided is no longer functioning and patients including babies have been evacuated, putting the enclave's collapsing health services in further peril, a World Health Organization official said on Monday.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:43:40 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 3DFN6COWCNNYVBSYOV632ZYTO4</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/raided-gaza-hospital-not-functioning-病人-evacuated-who-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Moldovan PM says anti-aircraft system needed to counter Russia]]></title><description><![CDATA[Prime Minister Dorin Recean said on Monday that Moldova needed an upgraded anti-aircraft defence system to counter threats from Russia heightened by Moscow's invasion of Ukraine, its eastern neighbour.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:21:01 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 5SACZG424VJNVLJK253IRFOBKI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/moldovan-pm-says-anti-aircraft-system-needed-counter-Russia-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Alexander Tanas]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[In Paris, UK's Cameron to call for stronger European coordination on Gaza]]></title><description><![CDATA[British foreign minister David Cameron will call for increased coordination between allies to address the "desperate" humanitarian situation in Gaza during a visit to Paris and Rome on Tuesday, his office said.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:07:00 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> KA2NLACCMRP4FM5646RFN4IYN4</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/paris-uks-cameron-call-stronger-european-coordination-gaza-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[White House plans one more Ukraine aid package, then up to Congress]]></title><description><![CDATA[President Joe Biden is planning one more military aid package in December for Ukraine in its war against Russia, the White House said on Monday, then further assistance to Kyiv will require an agreement in Congress where prospects for a deal were uncertain.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:04:30 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> B2CZZ6SOUFNSZLTRDNQFSRV3XM</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/us/white-house-plans-one-more-ukraine-aid-package-then-up-congress-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美国</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[US-led Red Sea patrol force to respond to attacks by Houthis]]></title><description><![CDATA[Several countries have agreed to jointly carry out patrols in the southern Red Sea and Gulf of Aden to try to safeguard commercial shipping against attacks by Yemen's Houthi rebels, who say they are supporting Palestinians under siege by Israel in the Gaza Strip.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 23:52:02 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 6NF7X2O6IZIPNM64HF7XN7DDNI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/joint-patrols-guard-ships-response-attacks-by-houthis-backing-palestinians-2023-12-18/<author><![CDATA[Bassam Masoud, Phil Stewart, James Mackenzie]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Australians assess flood damages from cyclone as rescue efforts ramp up]]></title><description><![CDATA[Residents in Australia's northeast on Tuesday took stock of flood damages from former Tropical Cyclone Jasper and authorities accelerated efforts to rescue people stranded in remote towns as rivers stayed above dangerous levels.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 22:51:45 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> X66NO234LVO75H44RGWW6IRQDE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australians-assess-flood-damages-cyclone-rescue-efforts-ramp-up-2023-12-18/<author><![CDATA[Renju Jose]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[North Korea says Hwasong-18 ICBM test was response to US hostility]]></title><description><![CDATA[North Korea said on Tuesday it had tested the isolated state's newest ICBM on Monday to gauge the war readiness of its nuclear force against mounting U.S. hostility, as Washington and its allies began operating a real-time missile data sharing system.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 22:51:13 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> KB266J5RLJNZZF6MN5K7E3E6ZE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/north-korea-says-it-conducted-hwasong-18-icbm-monday-yonhap-2023-12-18/<author><![CDATA[Jack Kim]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Iceland volcano erupts near town after weeks of quake activity]]></title><description><![CDATA[A volcano erupted late on Monday in southwest Iceland, spewing lava and smoke across a wide area after weeks of intense earthquake activity, the country's Meteorological Office said, threatening a nearby town.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Dec 2023 22:48:16 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> ZMXKCQ5AGFNSTEOYCV62ZIVMPE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/iceland-volcano-erupts-after-weeks-quake-activity-2023-12-18/<author><![CDATA[Terje Solsvik]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item></channel></rss>