<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/reuters/world" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[Reuters.com is your online source for the latest world news stories and current events, ensuring our readers up to date with any breaking news developments - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><image/><url> https://www.reuters.com/pf/resources/images/reuters/logo-vertical-default-512x512.png?d=116</url><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/<lastbuilddate> 2024 年 2 月 26 日星期一 06:08:41 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Mexico president lambastes YouTube after company edits video revealing NYT journalist's number]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador criticized YouTube on Sunday night after the tech company removed the video of a news conference in which the leader revealed the private telephone number of the New York Times' Mexico bureau chief.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 05:22:38 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> ZIJTTT5PBNNOLPJBAGHZSM22JY</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/mexico-president-lambastes-youtube-after-company-edits-video-revealing-nyt-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA['Not in dreamland': WTO aims for modest outcomes at Abu Dhabi meeting]]></title><description><![CDATA[Trade ministers from nearly every country in the world gather in Abu Dhabi on Monday for a World Trade Organization meeting that aims to set new global commerce rules, but even its ambitious chief Ngozi Okonjo-Iweala has sought to curb expectations.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 03:07:04 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> A6QXSXLWIJMDXG5G5WR2JYHML4</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/not-dreamland-wto-aims-modest-outcomes-abu-dhabi-meeting-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Emma Farge, Rachna Uppal]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anti-Muslim hate speech soars in India, research group says]]></title><description><![CDATA[Anti-Muslim hate speech in India rose by 62% in the second half of 2023 compared to the first six months of the year, a Washington-based research group said on Monday, adding the Israel-Gaza war played a key role in the last three months.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 03:04:26 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> J26KU3QWT5MX3PPMQ5RYX7MDUY</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/india/anti-muslim-hate-speech-soars-india-research-group-says-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Kanishka Singh]]></author><category>世界</category><category>印度</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[US says Yemen's Houthis ballistic missile misses US tanker Torm Thor]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. Central Command (CENTCOM) said early on Monday that Yemen's Houthis launched one anti-ship ballistic missile likely targeting the MV Torm Thor, but missed the U.S.-flagged, owned and operated oil tanker, in the Gulf of Aden on Feb. 24.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 02:57:37 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> BTGQRXFHNBOOJI7SX2YHZIVO64</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/us-says-yemens-houthis-ballistic-missile-misses-us-tanker-torm-thor-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[South Korea gives protesting doctors end-Feb deadline to return to work]]></title><description><![CDATA[South Korea's government on Monday told young doctors they had until the end of February to return to work or risk being punished for staging a week-long protest that has disrupted services for patients at several major hospitals.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 02:43:11 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> CU6WCNZ2G5OKJJC7IF4FKIANOA</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/skorea-doctors-may-be-suspended-unless-they-return-work-official-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Jack Kim, Ju-Min Park]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[New Zealand begins sentencing of those involved in White Island volcanic eruption]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sentencing for the tour booking agents and managers of an island in New Zealand where a volcanic eruption killed 22 people, mostly tourists, in 2019 began on Monday, with the prosecutor warning those sentenced may not be able to pay a fine.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 02:34:49 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 3RRQLYGEUNNEDIL5KXKWACCWWM</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/new-zealand-begins-sentencing-those-involved-white-island-volcanic-eruption-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Lucy Craymer]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hungary set to ratify Sweden's NATO accession, clearing last hurdle]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hungary is expected to ratify Sweden's NATO accession on Monday, clearing the last hurdle before the historic step by the Nordic country whose neutrality lasted through two world wars and the simmering conflict of the Cold War.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 02:09:08 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> W37LEVDDR5LX7IMMTJPTVJTZII</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/hungary-set-ratify-swedens-nato-accession-clearing-last-hurdle-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Krisztina Than, Niklas Pollard]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Canada's finance minister says pharmacare deal no fiscal threat, Globe and Mail reports]]></title><description><![CDATA[A "pharmacare" deal between Canada's ruling Liberals and the New Democrats (NDP) will not threaten the country's fiscal standing, Finance Minister Chrystia Freeland told a news conference on Sunday, The Globe and Mail reported.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:48:32 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> OKZK4EYUJRK7LIZ3JYLCCHGUBU</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-finance-minister-says-pharmacare-deal-no-fiscal-threat-globe-mail-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[South Korea doctors on mass walkout say they are overworked and unheard]]></title><description><![CDATA[Young doctors say their pay and working conditions should be the priority, rather than a government plan to boost physician ranks. Authorities say more staff are needed for remote areas and one of the world's most rapidly ageing societies.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:40:06 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> OCBFZ4EJGFMVFHL7ATXD4N4BUU</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/overworked-unheard-south-korean-doctors-mass-walkout-say-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Ju-Min Park, Minwoo Park]]></author><category>商业</category><category>工作世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[China seeks to strengthen cooperation with New Zealand for CPTPP, commerce minister says]]></title><description><![CDATA[China is willing to work with New Zealand to continue strengthening cooperation in the process of joining The Comprehensive and Progressive Agreement for Trans-Pacific Partnership, its commerce minister said.]]></description><pubDate> Sun, 25 Feb 2024 23:40:59 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> DGNSCQ3FBJPAXO3BTCAMGFB6PM</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/china-seeks-strengthen-cooperation-with-new-zealand-cptpp-commerce-minister-says-2024-02-25/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Taiwan ally Tuvalu names Feleti Teo as new prime minister]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tuvalu on Monday announced former attorney general and fisheries official Feleti Teo as its new prime minister, after he was elected unopposed by lawmakers in the Pacific Islands nation, officials said.]]></description><pubDate> Sun, 25 Feb 2024 22:37:29 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> RSW6LNS66JLUVJMJULRQMG2KYI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/tuvalu-name-new-prime-minister-monday-2024-02-25/<author><![CDATA[Kirsty Needham]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item></channel></rss>