<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/reuters/world" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[Reuters.com is your online source for the latest world news stories and current events, ensuring our readers up to date with any breaking news developments - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><image/><url> https://www.reuters.com/pf/resources/images/reuters/logo-vertical-default-512x512.png?d=116</url><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/<lastbuilddate> 2024 年 1 月 18 日星期四 15:13:38 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Romania's government plans first measures for protesting farmers, truckers -media]]></title><description><![CDATA[Romania's government unveiled a first package of measures to aid farmers and truckers whose widening protests against high business costs have hit a border crossing with Ukraine and elsewhere in the country, local media reported on Thursday.]]></description><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 15:04:20 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> QDRINHVQKRNR3HH27BFIQSUQ34</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/romanias-government-plans-first-measures-protesting-farmers-truckers-media-2024-01-18/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hungary to limit visas for temporary workers from outside the EU]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hungary will limit the number of visas issued to temporary workers from outside the European Union and also ban them from certain professions in a bid to protect local jobs, the Economy Ministry said on Thursday.]]></description><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 14:53:54 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> ZK2ZKAGPS5NMDC66GKJ22SSGDA</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/hungary-limit-visas-temporary-workers-outside-eu-2024-01-18/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[NATO to kick off biggest drills in decades with some 90,000 troops]]></title><description><![CDATA[Around 90,000 troops will participate in NATO's largest exercise for decades, known as Steadfast Defender 2024, that will kick off next week and run through to May, the alliance's top commander Chris Cavoli said on Thursday.]]></description><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 14:39:05 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 5ASWB25TARJTXGXVD3DTKPOO6Y</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/nato-kick-off-biggest-drills-decades-with-some-90000-troops-2024-01-18/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[France denies Russia's claims that it has mercenaries in Ukraine]]></title><description><![CDATA[France denied on Thursday claims made earlier by Russia that there were French mercenaries in Ukraine, as it responded to a statement made earlier this week by Russia's defence ministry that Russia had killed French mercenaries in Kharkiv.]]></description><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 14:27:30 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> W4KTZWIFKBOJDBJFKGJVJDAUGE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/france-denies- Russias-claims-that-it-has-mercenaries-ukraine-2024-01-18/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Slovak president urges lawmakers to rethink criminal law reform, PM Fico unswayed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Slovak president Zuzana Caputova urged lawmakers on Thursday to reconsider plans to scrap a special prosecution office for high crimes and lower sentences for financial crimes, proposals that have raised concerns over rule of law.]]></description><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 14:16:55 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 7OTL5WZ43NPUTI6MIMBK4LD53A</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/slovak-president-urges-lawmakers-rethink-criminal-law-reform-pm-fico-unswayed-2024-01-18/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Suez Canal diversions pile pressure on Egypt's distressed economy]]></title><description><![CDATA[A sharp downturn in revenue after sea attacks by Yemen's Houthis diverted away shipping away from the Suez Canal has struck a painful new blow to Egypt's already deteriorating economy, adding urgency to the need for reforms and help from abroad.]]></description><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 14:08:51 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> WH47IYDSPJM5HC7VW5TITGPIMU</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/suez-canal-diversions-pile-Pressure-egypts-distressed-economy-2024-01-18/<author><![CDATA[Patrick Werr]]></author><category>世界</category><category>非洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Explainer: How the West might use Russia's frozen reserves]]></title><description><![CDATA[Western officials say they are open to the idea of confiscating $300-350 billion of frozen Russian financial assets to help support Ukraine, but how that would be done remains highly complex given it would set a controversial precedent.]]></description><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 14:08:06 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> PBINNRN3S5ICPAYUBZLJCP3N7E</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/how-west-might-use-Russias-frozen-reserves-2024-01-18/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Indonesia allows Boeing 737 MAX 9 planes to fly again after checks]]></title><description><![CDATA[Indonesia has allowed three Boeing 737 MAX 9 planes to fly again after grounding them, as they have different configurations from a jet that was forced to make an emergency landing in the United States on Jan. 5, its transport ministry said on Thursday.]]></description><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 13:59:16 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> Z6QQE5M3CJIOPDDYATK76PLIBU</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/indonesia-allows-boeing-737-max-9-planes-fly-again-after-checks-2024-01-18/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sri Lanka to continue drug crackdown despite rights group concerns - minister]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sri Lanka vowed to continue an anti-narcotics campaign that has seen more than 35,000 people detained over the last few weeks despite concerns raised by multiple rights groups, top officials said on Thursday.]]></description><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 13:56:54 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> AQKNWISRKNKHTAP33WGKNFTKCE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/sri-lanka-continue-drug-crackdown-尽管-rights-group-concerns-minister-2024-01-18/<author><![CDATA[Uditha Jayasinghe]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exclusive: Saudi Arabia still considering BRICS membership, sources say]]></title><description><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia is still considering an invitation to become a member of the BRICS bloc of countries after being asked to join by the grouping last year, two sources with direct knowledge of the matter told Reuters on Thursday.]]></description><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 13:48:54 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> IFZJFKFFLJP4JIRAO5GOT6D4UU</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/saudi-arabia-considering-brics-membership-sources-2024-01-18/<author><![CDATA[Maha Dahan, Dmitry Zhdannikov]]></author><category>商业</category><category>达沃斯</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Somalia rejects mediation efforts with Ethiopia over port deal]]></title><description><![CDATA[Somalia rejected any discussions with Ethiopia about Addis Ababa's agreement to lease a port in the breakaway region of Somaliland, as regional heads of state gathered on Thursday to try to defuse a growing diplomatic crisis.]]></description><pubDate> Thu, 18 Jan 2024 13:18:01 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> UOI45ECIKBLYHKAY42AJL74CWE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/somalia-rejects-mediation-efforts-with-ethiopia-over-port-deal-2024-01-18/<author><![CDATA[Giulia Paravicini, Dawit Endeshaw]]></author><category>世界</category><category>非洲</category></item></channel></rss>