<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/reuters/world" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[Reuters.com is your online source for the latest world news stories and current events, ensuring our readers up to date with any breaking news developments - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><image/><url> https://www.reuters.com/pf/resources/images/reuters/logo-vertical-default-512x512.png?d=116</url><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/<lastbuilddate> 2023 年 12 月 20 日星期三 00:26:36 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Russia launches air assault on Kyiv for fifth time in December -Ukraine]]></title><description><![CDATA[Russia late on Tuesday launched its fifth air attack this month targeting Kyiv, with Ukraine's air defence systems destroying all weapons on approach to the Ukrainian capital, Kyiv's military said early on Wednesday.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 23:30:22 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> FGUXQWP43FKVBPF7LYFBW2Z2LM</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ Russia-launches-air-assault-kyiv-fifth-time-december-ukraine-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trump barred from Colorado ballot for role in attack on US Capitol]]></title><description><![CDATA[Former President Donald Trump cannot appear on the ballot in Colorado in next year's presidential election due to his role in the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the U.S. Capitol by his supporters, the state's top court ruled Tuesday in a historic judgment that is likely to find its way to the U.S. Supreme Court.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 23:19:30 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 23NWZCWJZJMPTCQMOSG47R3NAE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/legal/colorado-supreme-court-disqualizes-trump-holding-office-filing-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>合法的</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ecuador approves tax reform, including an amnesty to boost youth jobs]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ecuador's National Assembly on Tuesday approved a tax amnesty proposed by President Daniel Noboa aimed at coaxing delinquent taxpayers to pay outstanding bills, part of a tax reform that also includes new incentives to employ young people.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 22:36:28 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 7W5YK66XABLNHJQV4YCZOARM3Y</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/ecuador-approves-tax-reform-include-an-amnesty-boost-youth-jobs-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[UN vote on Gaza delayed another day amid talks to avoid US veto]]></title><description><![CDATA[A United Nations Security Council vote on a bid to boost aid deliveries to the Gaza Strip has been delayed by another day as talks continue to try and avoid a third U.S. veto of action over the two-month long Israel-Hamas war, diplomats said on Tuesday.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 21:37:20 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> QJRXIHM4LJNH5FWWLOQASIJP74</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/un-vote-gaza-delayed-another-day-amid-talks-avoid-us-veto-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Michelle Nichols]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Attacks on ships in Red Sea must stop, White House says]]></title><description><![CDATA[Attacks by Iran-backed Yemeni militants in the Red Sea must stop and the U.S. and its partners will continue to protect ships from being targeted, White House national security spokesperson John Kirby said on Tuesday.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 21:08:12 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> FN5CLZSLQNIFTAEMIIQU4KYE7M</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/attacks-ships-red-sea-must-stop-white-house-says-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Islamic Jihad releases video of two Israeli hostages pleading for their release]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Al Quds Brigades, the armed wing of the Palestinian Islamic Jihad movement, released a video of two male Israeli hostages in Gaza pleading for their release on its Telegram account on Tuesday.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 21:02:13 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> RYMQO6BV6VKFND2TBCBMEVTMXM</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/islamic-jihad-releases-video-two-male-israeli-hostages-pleading-their-release-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[US-formed coalition in Red Sea part of aggression against Palestinians, Yemen's Houthis say]]></title><description><![CDATA[The international coalition formed by the U.S. to protect maritime navigation in the Red Sea is part of the aggression against the Palestinian people, the political bureau of Yemen's Houthi group said in a statement on Tuesday, adding that the coalition contradicts international law.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 20:51:44 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> BQPI6BDIWZKHBCDFWVJMVQLT5M</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/us-formed-coalition-red-sea-part-aggression-against-palestinians-yemens-houthis-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Biden welcomes Pope decision to allow blessings for same-sex couples]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. President Joe Biden welcomed the decision by Pope Francis to allow Roman Catholic priests to administer blessings to same-sex couples as long as they are not part of regular Church rituals or liturgies, White House spokesperson Karine Jean Pierre said on Tuesday.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 19:58:14 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> Q7QYYG4MUFIXZDMUGWJMBKXCIM</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/biden-welcomes-pope-decision-allow-blessings-same-sex- Couples-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ex-Haitian senator sentenced to life in prison over president's assassination]]></title><description><![CDATA[Former Haitian Senator John Joel Joseph was on Tuesday sentenced in a Miami court to life in prison over his role in the July 2021 assassination of Haiti's last president, Jovenel Moise.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 19:50:53 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> TKQOVJMY4NNDHHUTEK5WT63EFI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/ex-haitian-senator-sentenced-life-prison-over-presidents-assassination-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thousands of Slovaks continue protesting government's criminal law reforms]]></title><description><![CDATA[At least 15,000 people demonstrated in Slovakia's capital on Tuesday as protests grew against plans of Prime Minister Robert Fico's government to fast-track criminal law changes that include scrapping a special prosecutor's office focused on corruption.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 19:44:11 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 3JFHT6GWNRMADKPVLYDXWX6C6Y</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/thousands-slovaks-continue-protesting-governments-criminal-law-reforms-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Radovan Stoklasa]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[EU, US urge Serbia to address concerns about electoral process]]></title><description><![CDATA[The European Union and the United States urged Serbia to address concerns about its electoral process after independent observers found worrying irregularities including vote buying during Sunday's snap election.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 19 Dec 2023 19:32:49 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> M7HEDH6SXBPDHDIKGQEZB6FG5A</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/eu-us-urge-serbia-address-concerns-about-electoral-process-2023-12-19/<author><![CDATA[Daphne Psaledakis, Kanishka Singh]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item></channel></rss>