<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/<atom:link href="http://rsshub.app/reuters/world" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[Reuters.com is your online source for the latest world news stories and current events, ensuring our readers up to date with any breaking news developments - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><image/><url> https://www.reuters.com/pf/resources/images/reuters/logo-vertical-default-512x512.png?d=116</url><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/<lastbuilddate> 2024 年 3 月 10 日星期日 17:18:05 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[St. Petersburg airport resumes operations after drone shot down in nearby region]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pulkovo airport in Saint Petersburg has resumed operations as Russian Defence Ministry said a Ukrainian drone was shot down in the neighbouring Leningrad region on Sunday.]]></description><pubDate> Sun, 10 Mar 2024 15:56:24 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> BMS7774MTNNIPG4HMVMAWAC5MU</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/st-petersburg-airport-resumes-operations-after-drone-shot-down-nearby-region-2024-03-10/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Egypt in touch with Hamas and Israel in search of Gaza ceasefire deal, sources say]]></title><description><![CDATA[Egypt was in contact with senior Hamas and Israeli figures as well as other mediators on Sunday in an effort to restart negotiations for a truce in the Gaza Strip during the Muslim holy month of Ramadan, which begins on Monday or Tuesday, two Egyptian security sources said.]]></description><pubDate> Sun, 10 Mar 2024 15:28:28 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> PGYG2EGVC5OFFOWDUCE6CNDUOM</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/egypt-touch-with-hamas-israel-search-gaza-ceasefire-deal-sources-say-2024-03-10/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gaza aid ship waiting to sail from Cyprus as charity builds jetty, source says]]></title><description><![CDATA[A ship carrying tonnes of food for Gaza remained docked in a Cyprus port on Sunday as preparations were underway to launch a yet untested maritime aid route to the enclave, where the United Nations estimates a quarter of the population [USN:L2N3FJ212 TEXT:"faces starvation"].]]></description><pubDate> Sun, 10 Mar 2024 15:19:46 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> NDPTTCX2PJKPRHL3LWFQQU5VUI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/gaza-aid-ship-waiting-sail-cyprus-charity-builds-jetty-source-says-2024-03-10/<author><![CDATA[Yiannis Kourtoglou, Stamos Prousalis]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[US, Jordan airdrop more aid to Gaza, US military says]]></title><description><![CDATA[The United States and Jordan carried out a new airdrop of humanitarian aid to Gaza's Palestinians on Sunday, parachuting in more than 11,500 meals, the U.S. military said.]]></description><pubDate> Sun, 10 Mar 2024 14:12:45 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> OYXCRRZA7BLWLL7EQOM3DXMJJA</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/us-jordan-airdrop-more-aid-gaza-us-military-says-2024-03-10/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sudan army general rules out Ramadan truce unless RSF leaves civilian sites]]></title><description><![CDATA[There would be no truce in Sudan in the Islamic holy month of Ramadan unless the Rapid Support Forces (RSF) paramilitary group leaves the homes and sites of civilians, senior Sudanese armed forces General Yasser al-Atta said on Sunday.]]></description><pubDate> Sun, 10 Mar 2024 13:21:12 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> PELZRDKMCNLWZIRSKU3C2YDTEQ</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/sudan-army-general-rules-out-ramadan-truce-unless-rsf-leaves-civilian-sites-2024-03-10/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>非洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Central African bloc lifts Gabon sanctions]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Economic Community of Central African States agreed to lift sanctions on Gabon on Saturday and reintegrate it into the regional bloc, six months after suspending its membership in response to a coup that ousted President Ali Bongo.]]></description><pubDate> Sun, 10 Mar 2024 12:36:16 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> UM4Y7RDGFRIJLJSLQ5YVTQX3TU</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/central-african-bloc-lifts-gabon-sanctions-2024-03-10/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>非洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[US military airlifts embassy personnel from Haiti, bolsters security]]></title><description><![CDATA[The U.S. military said on Sunday it has carried out an operation in Haiti to airlift non-essential embassy personnel from the country and added U.S. forces bolster embassy security, as Caribbean nation reels under a state of emergency.]]></description><pubDate> Sun, 10 Mar 2024 12:13:32 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> CO27EBV7TZO5XF7MMZ6ANY7SKU</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/us-military-airlifts-embassy-personnel-haiti-bolsters-security-2024-03-10/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Israel's Herzog pleads for peace at Amsterdam Holocaust museum amid protest]]></title><description><![CDATA[Israeli President Isaac Herzog, attending an opening of a Holocaust museum in Amsterdam on Sunday, called for prayers for peace and the immediate release of hostages taken by Hamas in its Oct. 7 attack and still held by the Islamist militants.]]></description><pubDate> Sun, 10 Mar 2024 12:12:33 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 7A45YTD2YNNIZAR5IDY5HSZEM4</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/israels-herzog-opens-holocaust-museum-amsterdam-amid-protest-2024-03-10/ <author><![CDATA[Charlotte Van Campenhout, Piroschka Van De Wouw, Hilde Verweij]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Senegal opposition coalition promises new currency and revamp of oil contracts]]></title><description><![CDATA[A Senegalese opposition coalition backed by popular firebrand Ousmane Sonko launched its presidential campaign platform on Saturday with promises to create a new national currency and renegotiate mining and energy contracts.]]></description><pubDate> Sun, 10 Mar 2024 11:54:44 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 3HMHDBCLXBOC5DPQMRDKEIX6QU</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/senegal-opposition-coalition-promises-new-currency-revamp-oil-contracts-2024-03-10/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>非洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Swiss police search for six missing skiers near Matterhorn]]></title><description><![CDATA[Police in Switzerland's Valais canton on Sunday were searching for six people who went missing during a ski tour that departed from the Alpine town of Zermatt.]]></description><pubDate> Sun, 10 Mar 2024 11:48:05 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> T2OW7OSGKZMF5CRBPP2MPK3H7A</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/swiss-police-search-six-missing-skiers-near-matterhorn-2024-03-10/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Palestinians prepare for Ramadan in the shadow of Gaza war]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hopes for a ceasefire, which would have allowed Ramadan to pass peacefully and enabled the return of at least some of the 134 Israeli hostages held in Gaza, appear to have been disappointed, with talks in Cairo apparently stalled.]]></description><pubDate> Sun, 10 Mar 2024 11:30:48 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> R2BNHETO4JJOPBDV2FN5KBNUJI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/palestinians-prepare-ramadan-shadow-gaza-war-2024-03-10/<author><![CDATA[Sinan Abu Mayzer. Nidal Al-Mughrabi. Bassam Masoud]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东</category></item></channel></rss>