<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/<atom:link href="http://rsshub.app/reuters/world" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[Reuters.com is your online source for the latest world news stories and current events, ensuring our readers up to date with any breaking news developments - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><image/><url> https://www.reuters.com/pf/resources/images/reuters/logo-vertical-default-512x512.png?d=116</url><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/<lastbuilddate> 2024 年 3 月 18 日星期一 20:19:34 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[EU Foreign Ministers approved sanctions in relation to Navalny's death]]></title><description><![CDATA[Foreign Ministers of the European Union member states on Monday approved sanctions against individuals and institutions in relation to the death of Russian opposition leader Alexei Navalny, Spanish Foreign Minister Jose Manuel Albares told reporters on Monday after meeting with his EU counterparts.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Mar 2024 17:55:31 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> TW7CGCI7VVJADHN4PHIN5KCLVI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/eu-foreign-ministers-approved-sanctions-relationship-navalnys-death-2024-03-18/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Looming Rafah incursion would 'break' Gaza aid distribution, UN says]]></title><description><![CDATA[The United Nations humanitarian coordinator said on Monday an Israeli assault on Rafah would leave Gaza aid distribution "broken" as the organisation would be unable to prepare enough supplies for the already displaced people fleeing the area.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Mar 2024 17:45:41 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> ZOV6WBXFCJN6NOUDEDCK5QBA2I</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/looming-rafah-incursion-could-break-gaza-aid-distribution-un-says-2024-03-18/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[US, Japan urge nations not to deploy nuclear weapons in orbit]]></title><description><![CDATA[The United States and Japan on Monday proposed a U.N. Security Council resolution stressing that nations should comply with a treaty that bars putting nuclear weapons in space, a message that appeared aimed at Russia.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Mar 2024 17:38:50 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> YPVRLFMSGVKADOPWV4XSAK452E</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/us-japan-urges-nations-not-to-deploy-nuclear-weapons-orbit-2024-03-18/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[US says seeking information on reports of detained Al Jazeera reporter in Gaza]]></title><description><![CDATA[The United States is aware of reports that an Al Jazeera journalist was detained by Israeli Defense Forces, State Department deputy spokesperson Vedant Patel told a news briefing on Monday, adding that Washington has sought information from Israel on the incident.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Mar 2024 17:33:08 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> F54Q7AVSBFIC3KDQPRJR5I43IU</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/us-says-seeking-information-reports-detained-al-jazeera-reporter-in-gaza-2024-03-18/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Putin greets Moscow rally after election win]]></title><description><![CDATA[A day after securing a new six-year term, Russian President Vladimir Putin appeared briefly at an open-air concert on Red Square on Monday to mark the 10th anniversary of Russia's annexation of Crimea from Ukraine.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Mar 2024 17:18:05 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> OS3NOOIQWJKGHAC5ASQEYHJTGA</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/putin-greets-moscow-rally-after-election-win-2024-03-18/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Toronto police report surge in hate crimes against Jews, Muslims]]></title><description><![CDATA[The number of antisemitic and anti-Muslim hate crimes in Canada's largest city of Toronto have risen significantly during the war in Gaza that followed Hamas' deadly Oct. 7 attack inside Israel, Toronto police said on Monday.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Mar 2024 17:03:37 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> HCPJGQSIDBKXXIRPDCK7OSGCRU</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/toronto-police-report-surge-hate-crimes-against-jews-muslims-2024-03-18/<author><![CDATA[Wa Lone, Kyawsoe Oo]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cuba summons top US diplomat, accuses US of stoking protests]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cuba's foreign ministry said it had summoned the top U.S. diplomat on the island to a meeting following protests on Sunday, accusing the U.S. embassy in Havana of seeking to stoke a broader anti-government uprising and meddling in Cuba's internal affairs.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:58:25 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> T2W3P2HS6VKDNONEESPDPBIVM3Q</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/cuban-government-says-we-stoked- Five-protests-weekend-2024-03-18/<author><![CDATA[Dave Sherwood]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Egyptians thought Regeni was British spy, Italian court told]]></title><description><![CDATA[Egyptian police detained an Italian student in Cairo because they thought he was a British spy, taking him to a security facility where he was tortured and murdered, an Italian prosecutor told a Rome court on Monday.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:45:45 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> H6XX7UWWG5JCREEICGUUEHGE54</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/egyptians-thought-regeni-was-british-spy-italian-court-told-2024-03-18/<author><![CDATA[Crispian Balmer]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Argentina economy set for third straight year-on-year contraction in Q4]]></title><description><![CDATA[Argentina's gross domestic product (GDP) is expected to have shrunk 1.5% year-on-year in the final quarter of 2023, the third straight annualized contraction, hit by declines in virtually all sectors of the economy, a Reuters poll found.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:30:36 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> IYI7C2XLAJIF5J5CBYOVFDAMTU</guid><link/>阿根廷经济连续第三季度同比收缩-2024-03-18/<author><![CDATA[Hernan Nessi]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[US warned Niger about ties to Russia, Iran before junta revoked accord, Pentagon says]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. officials traveled to Niger last week to express concerns about the country's potential development of ties to Russia and Iran before the ruling junta on Saturday revoked an accord governing the roughly 1,000 U.S. military personnel there, the Pentagon said on Monday.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:28:28 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> FHZJPAOSCVPRFO6JRFOSVDDODI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/us-warned-niger-about-ties-Russia-iran-before-junta-revoked-pentagon-accord-2024-03-18/<author><![CDATA[Phil Stewart]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Israel asks World Court not to order new measures over Gaza hunger]]></title><description><![CDATA[Israel has asked the International Court of Justice (ICJ) not to issue emergency orders for it to step up humanitarian aid to Gaza to address a looming famine, dismissing South Africa's request to do so as "morally repugnant".]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:53:31 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> QUDSGXTOYFLFFMCTQGBQ324X7U</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israel-asks-world-court-not-order-new-measures-over-gaza-famine-2024-03-18/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东地区</category></item></channel></rss>