<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/reuters/world" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[Reuters.com is your online source for the latest world news stories and current events, ensuring our readers up to date with any breaking news developments - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><image/><url> https://www.reuters.com/pf/resources/images/reuters/logo-vertical-default-512x512.png?d=116</url><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/<lastbuilddate> 2024 年 2 月 14 日星期三 01:59:27 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Two-thirds of Jewish Americans feel less secure than before Oct. 7]]></title><description><![CDATA[About two-thirds of Jewish Americans felt less secure in late 2023 than they did a year earlier, according to a survey mostly conducted after the Hamas attack on Israel on Oct. 7 and released on Tuesday.]]></description><pubDate> Wed, 14 Feb 2024 01:54:31 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 3E3V26S3Z5PT5HIDUUMKJVYQHY</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/us/two-thirds-jewish-americans-feel-less-secure-than-before-oct-7-2024-02-14/<author><![CDATA[Kanishka Singh]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美国</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Peru's president reshuffles cabinet, tapping new economy and energy chiefs]]></title><description><![CDATA[Peruvian President Dina Boluarte named replacements on Tuesday for four key members of her cabinet, including a new economy chief as well as a new energy and mining minister, with both set to face a fragile economy that last year dipped into recession.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Feb 2024 23:41:24 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> RZF4H27UQBLHPDFU6J5JORSDP4</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/perus-president-replaces-economy-energy-ministers-2024-02-13/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wild weather cuts power, sparks bushfires in Australia]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hundreds of thousands of residents across Australia's Victoria state remained without power on Wednesday after wild weather knocked down transmission lines and sparked bushfires that injured five firefighters.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Feb 2024 23:15:06 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> GCOOPOQR4NMRDGJ5ZB3BTOYXVQ</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/strong-winds-cause-power-outages-fan-bushfires-australias-southeast-2024-02-13/<author><![CDATA[Renju Jose]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Russia's parliament to vote on suspending Moscow's OSCE participation]]></title><description><![CDATA[Russia's parliament will vote on Feb. 21 on suspending the country's participation in the Parliamentary Assembly of the Organization for Security and Co-operation (OSCE), Duma Speaker Vyacheslav Volodin said on Tuesday.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Feb 2024 23:12:58 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> YDS7B6NK2ZPZFDGSNFYM3J2K4Y</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ Russias-parliament-vote-suspending-moscows-osce-participation-2024-02-13/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[US urges Senegalese President Sall to restore Senegal's electoral calendar]]></title><description><![CDATA[U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken on Tuesday urged Senegalese President Macky Sall to restore Senegal's electoral calendar and timeline for presidential transition, the U.S. State Department said after a call between the two leaders.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Feb 2024 22:41:03 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 6Q3IUT4DKRNOBOAFN2EJDVXZJI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/africa/us-urges-senegalese-president-sall-restore-senegals-electoral-calendar-2024-02-13/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>非洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[UK to urge allies to boost defence production for Ukraine]]></title><description><![CDATA[British Foreign Secretary David Cameron will urge allies to increase defence production to help Ukraine's war with Russia, his office said on Tuesday ahead of a diplomatic tour to Bulgaria, Poland and Germany.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Feb 2024 22:33:54 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> S3NJKX54ZFMNNIVEXNB2ETWBY4</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/uk-urge-allies-boost-defence-production-ukraine-2024-02-13/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>英国</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Indonesians vote to replace Jokowi, floods disrupt some polling]]></title><description><![CDATA[Indonesians started voting on Wednesday in areas across the archipelago in an election headlined by the race to succeed popular President Joko Widodo, whose influence could determine who takes the helm of the world's third-largest democracy.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Feb 2024 21:02:11 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> ZWSJFFZWRFKGZHUKAQDD5DEVJA</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/indonesia-votes-new-president-under-shadow-influenceial-incumbent-2024-02-13/<author><![CDATA[Fransiska Nangoy, Bernadette Christina]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[US reviewing reports of civilian harm by Israel, State Dept says]]></title><description><![CDATA[The United States is reviewing reports that Israel has harmed civilians in its war in Gaza under a set of guidelines aimed at ensuring countries receiving U.S. arms conduct military operations in line with international humanitarian law, State Department spokesperson Matthew Miller said on Tuesday.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Feb 2024 20:55:58 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 7QLV3Y2YI5MTXNG2QKMZESRH5Y</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/us-reviewing-reports-civilian-harm-by-israel-state-dept-says-2024-02-13/<author><![CDATA[Humeyra Pamuk, Simon Lewis]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Haitian gangs' growing funds, arsenals challenge planned intervention -report]]></title><description><![CDATA[Haitian gangs are increasingly economically autonomous, a Geneva-based criminal research group warned, using funds coerced from private businesses, local residents and families of kidnapping victims to pay for guns and soldiers.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Feb 2024 20:31:19 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> UIZFFP2U6ZMNHP4FNI5VEUKCHA</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/haitian-gangs-grinding-funds-arsenals-challenge-planned-intervention-report-2024-02-13/<author><![CDATA[Sarah Morland]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ukraine defence minister, new armed forces chief inform Western generals of Kyiv's plans]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ukraine Defence Minister Rustem Umerov and newly appointed armed forces commander Oleksandr Syrskyi discussed Kyiv's military plans for 2024 with the supreme commander of the NATO Armed Forces in Europe and the commander of the Security Assistance Group Ukraine, Umerov said on Facebook on Tuesday.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Feb 2024 20:13:08 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 7UKZGQJE7ZLBRPSKKQYFMPRBPE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ukraine-defence-minister-new-armed-forces-chief-inform-western-generals-kyivs-2024-02-13/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trinidad and Tobago cleans up beaches following 12-kilometer oil spill]]></title><description><![CDATA[First responders and volunteers from Trinidad and Tobago on Tuesday sought to contain an oil spill detected last week in the Caribbean country's waters and clean areas of Tobago island's coast already affected by the incident.]]></description><pubDate> Tue, 13 Feb 2024 19:25:43 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> VFOFS6B5Q5LF5GNF3IARSPMM24</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trinidad-tobago-cleans-up-beaches-following-12-kilometer-oil-spill-2024-02-13/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>可持续发展</category><category>气候与能源</category></item></channel></rss>