<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/ <atom:link href="https://rsshub.app/reuters/world" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><description><![CDATA[Reuters.com is your online source for the latest world news stories and current events, ensuring our readers up to date with any breaking news developments - Made with love by RSSHub(https://github.com/DIYgod/RSSHub)]]></description><generator> RS集线器</generator><webmaster>i@diygod.me (DIYgod)</webmaster><language> zh-cn</language><image/><url> https://www.reuters.com/pf/resources/images/reuters/logo-vertical-default-512x512.png?d=116</url><title><![CDATA[World News | Latest Top Stories | Reuters]]></title><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/<lastbuilddate> 2024 年 2 月 26 日星期一 12:09:18 GMT</lastbuilddate><ttl> 120 </ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Venezuela's sudden policy change may stem from waning support for Maduro, sources say]]></title><description><![CDATA[Venezuela's recent abrupt reversal in its nascent rapprochement with the United States and domestic opponents is likely a response to declining support among its traditional base, according to sources close to the ruling party, voters and analysts.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 12:06:06 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> F5DFM6SRURL4JJBY7ACNJIR3XE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/venezuelas-sudden-policy-change-may-stem-waning-support-maduro-sources-say-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Mayela Armas, Vivian Sequera]]></author><category>世界</category><category>美洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Russian prosecutor seeks nearly 3 years in jail for rights campaigner Orlov]]></title><description><![CDATA[A Russian prosecutor requested a prison term of two years and 11 months on Monday for veteran human rights activist Oleg Orlov, who is on trial for discrediting Russia's armed forces, the Memorial human rights organisation said.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 11:32:04 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> U6P2HAUEFBOSHGBY3EUX6VRCOI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ Russian-prosecutor-seeks-nearly-3-years-jail-rights-campaigner-orlov-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Israel court hears challenges to religious draft waiver amid Gaza war]]></title><description><![CDATA[The top Israeli court heard challenges on Monday to exemptions granted to ultra-Orthodox Jews from military conscription, a long-standing source of friction with more secular citizens now stoked by the country's costly mobilisation in the Gaza war.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 11:08:50 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> T7YHW4FXJVLC3K6T7SGXKNOUGI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israel-court-hears-challenges-religious-draft-waiver-amid-gaza-war-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Explainer: Can Ukraine supporters force a US House vote on foreign aid?]]></title><description><![CDATA[If U.S. House of Representatives Speaker Mike Johnson refuses to allow a vote on the $95 billion foreign security aid bill passed by the Senate, its supporters may turn to rarely used and complicated procedural tools to try to force a vote.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 11:05:07 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> O5BMHVUMPBALEA75FPZIA4QZE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/can-ukraine-supporters-force-us-house-vote-foreign-aid-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Patricia Zengerle]]></author><category>世界</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Navalny was close to being freed in prisoner swap, says ally]]></title><description><![CDATA[Russian opposition politician Alexei Navalny was close to being freed in a prisoner swap at the time of his death, a close ally said on Monday, repeating an allegation by his family and supporters that President Vladimir Putin had him killed.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 11:00:57 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> 2OO3RRSQGROCTLLPRAVRMGE4EE</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/navalny-was-close-being-freed-prisoner-swap-says-ally-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Filipp Lebedev, Andrew Osborn]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kremlin calls claim that Russia pressured Alexei Navalny's mother absurd]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Kremlin on Monday called allegations that Russian authorities had pressured the mother of Alexei Navalny over her son's funeral absurd, saying President Vladimir Putin had not been involved in decisions on Navalny's body.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 10:59:40 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> NHJSU7ZZBNJZDIQNVAT5SY236A</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/kremlin-calls-claim-that-Russia-Pressured-alexei-navalnys-mother-absurd-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Israel strikes deeper into Lebanon as Hezbollah downs drone]]></title><description><![CDATA[Israel carried out airstrikes in Lebanon's Bekaa Valley on Monday, killing at least two Hezbollah members in its deepest attack yet into Lebanese territory since hostilities erupted with the Iran-backed group last October, sources in Lebanon said.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 10:52:26 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> H4S5CSPUMVLEXF3BHUHSOX4QXQ</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israel-strikes-deeper-into-lebanon-hezbollah-downs-drone-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>中东</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Russia says idea of Ukraine peace talks without Moscow is absurd]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Kremlin said on Monday that the idea of holding peace talks without Russia was ridiculous, after Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelenskiy said he hoped to hold a spring summit in Switzerland to discuss his peace vision with Kyiv's allies.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 10:43:51 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> MNZCPRATBRNJ3MQF63K32JIXXI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ Russia-says-idea-ukraine-peace-talks-without-moscow-is-absurd-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ukraine military confirms retreat from eastern village]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Ukrainian military confirmed on Monday its retreat from the village of Lastochkyne in eastern Ukraine, saying the move would help it halt the westward advance of Russian forces.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 10:32:09 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> GDW3FH7PEBMHZFULYE33MHNMWI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ukraine-military-confirms-retreat-eastern-village-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kremlin shrugs off latest Western sanctions against Russia]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Kremlin on Monday shrugged off the latest round of Western sanctions against Moscow, saying that Russia's economy had adapted to restrictions and that those imposing sanctions were hurting themselves with any new measures.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 10:30:55 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> EVSIBR3TWRI2NDU7YTJPTV5YXY</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/kremlin-shrugs-off-latest-western-sanctions-against-Russia-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Reuters]]></author><category>世界</category><category>欧洲</category></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nawaz Sharif's daughter elected to head Pakistan's Punjab, seen as stepping stone]]></title><description><![CDATA[Maryam Nawaz, the daughter of Pakistan's three-time former prime minister Nawaz Sharif, was elected on Monday as the head of the country's most populous province, Punjab, in a move underlining the expanding grip of the family in the South Asian nation.]]></description><pubDate> Mon, 26 Feb 2024 09:57:56 GMT</pubDate><guid ispermalink="false"> BQM3NYRC4FO2TPCSQVXXGL7ZUI</guid><link/> https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/nawaz-sharifs-daughter-elected-head-pakistans-punjab-seen-stepping-stone-2024-02-26/<author><![CDATA[Asif Shahzad, Mubasher Bukhari]]></author><category>世界</category><category>亚太地区</category></item></channel></rss>